[
    {
        "QuestionNum": "1",
        "Question": "What are the force sensitive beings in the Star Wars universe called?",
        "A": "Mandalorion",
        "B": "Jedi",
        "C": "Wookie",
        "D": "Jawa",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "2",
        "Question": "Which of these is a race in Star Wars?",
        "A": "Yuzzum",
        "B": "Salt Vampire",
        "C": "Gorn",
        "D": "Talosian",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "3",
        "Question": "What race is Yoda?",
        "A": "Ithorian",
        "B": "Trandoshan",
        "C": "Neimoidian",
        "D": "Unknown",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "4",
        "Question": "What type of ship do the Rebels use during their attempt to destroy the first Death Star?",
        "A": "U-wing",
        "B": "Y-wing",
        "C": "X-wing",
        "D": "B-wing",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "5",
        "Question": "What order is given by Emperor Palpatine in Revenge of the Sith?",
        "A": "66",
        "B": "52",
        "C": "99",
        "D": "45",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "6",
        "Question": "What planet does Luke find Yoda on?",
        "A": "Tatooine",
        "B": "Yavin 4",
        "C": "Kashyyk",
        "D": "Dagobah",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "7",
        "Question": "Who is the Weequay pirate that is shown prominently in the Clone Wars?",
        "A": "Cad Bane",
        "B": "Asajj Ventress",
        "C": "Shaak Ti",
        "D": "Hondo Ohnaka",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "8",
        "Question": "Luke had a secret sister that wasn't known until Return of the Jedi. Who was she?",
        "A": "Padm√©",
        "B": "Bo-Katan",
        "C": "Leia",
        "D": "Ahsoka",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "9",
        "Question": "Which planet was destroyed by the Death Star?",
        "A": "Alderaan",
        "B": "Hoth",
        "C": "Bespin",
        "D": "Mustafar",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "10",
        "Question": "Who is Lando's co-pilot in Return of the Jedi?",
        "A": "Greedo",
        "B": "Nien Nunb",
        "C": "Hera Syndulla",
        "D": "Maz kanata",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "11",
        "Question": "What is the name of Jango's, and later, Boba's ship?",
        "A": "Executor",
        "B": "Home One",
        "C": "Slave 1",
        "D": "Invisible Hand",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "12",
        "Question": "What species are the guards in Jabba's Palace?",
        "A": "Bothan",
        "B": "Duros",
        "C": "Er'Kit",
        "D": "Gamorrean",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "13",
        "Question": "What color is Yoda?",
        "A": "Green",
        "B": "Blue",
        "C": "Red",
        "D": "Pink",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "14",
        "Question": "Han Solo famously likes to state that the Millenium Falcon made the Kessel run in less than how many parsecs?",
        "A": "12",
        "B": "10",
        "C": "5",
        "D": "7",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "15",
        "Question": "Which hand does Luke lose when fighting Darth Vader?",
        "A": "Neither",
        "B": "Left",
        "C": "Both",
        "D": "Right",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "16",
        "Question": "What planet is Rey living on at the beginning of The Force Awakens?",
        "A": "Tatooine",
        "B": "Hoth",
        "C": "Jakku",
        "D": "Ryloth",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "17",
        "Question": "What two legged creatures are ridden by Rebels in Empire Strikes Back?",
        "A": "Tauntaun",
        "B": "Bantha",
        "C": "Rancor",
        "D": "Dewback",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "18",
        "Question": "Who is the Ewok that befriends Leia on Endor?",
        "A": "Nippet",
        "B": "Teebo",
        "C": "Wicket",
        "D": "Logray",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "19",
        "Question": "Who is the sarcastic droid that features in Rogue One?",
        "A": "BB-8",
        "B": "K-2SO",
        "C": "AP-5",
        "D": "4-LOM",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "20",
        "Question": "Which character is often seen by Jabba's side?",
        "A": "Pondo Babba",
        "B": "Salacious B Crumb",
        "C": "Dr. Cornelious Evazan",
        "D": "Hem Dazon",
        "Answer": "B"
    }
]